CHORUS SINGS:
♪ The Simpsons ♪
Ah.
(school bell ringing)
(Barney belches)
(whistle blows)
(yells)
(beeping)
(playing the blues)
Ooh!
(gunfire)
(tires screeching)
(horn honking. Grampa shouts)
D'oh!
(tires screeching)
(grunts)
(ominous music playing)
(thunder rumbling)
(light. gentle music plays)
(buzzing)
♪♪
(Homer chuckles)
Thanks to our new GPS.
I'll have you at school
in no time.
(Homer chuckles)
FEMALE VOICE:
Turn right in 50 meters.
Oh. meters?
Dad. a meter is three inches
longer than a yard.
which is 36 inches.
so 50 divided by 39
times 36 equals...
You have missed your turn.
Recalculating.
Turn right in .5 meters.
Dad. no.
That takes us
into a construction site.
Stupid kid thinks he's
smarter than a computer.
Seat belts. kids.
(tires squealing)
(Homer wailing)
Turn left. Turn right.
(Homer moaning)
Decrease elevation ten feet.
then turn left.
D'oh!
You have reached
your destination.
-Thanks for the ride.
-Bye. Dad!
Turn right in 2.3 kilometers...
Why. you...
(grunts)
Recalculating.
-So cold. So cold.
-(electronic crackling)
(children laughing and shouting)
(squeaks)
(swallows)
Where's Mrs. K.?
Mrs. Krabappel had
to go to Portland.
Apparently. the
people she hired
to deprogram her
sister from that cult
turned out to be an
even worse cult.
So. who's gonna
take her place?
Me. I hope.
Not you. Never you.
And due to budget cuts.
until Edna comes back.
I have no choice
but to merge
the school's two
fourth grade classes.
-(students gasping)
-The other fourth grade?
But they're so different
from us.
They have music
on Tuesdays.
Their teacher
takes her shoes off.
Their twins are
one boy. one girl.
Weird.
(sighs)
All right. new kids.
jam your chairs into
my kids' desks.
-Is anyone here?
-Oh. whatever.
-Whatever.
-Is anyone here?
'Sup? I'm Bodhi.
-Do you surf?
-No.
My parents took me
to Hawaii once.
but I was intimidated
by the physiques
of the local kids.
so I just stayed
in the hotel room.
That's cool.
No. it's not cool.
(grunts)
You are so dead.
Sorry. Let me get
that for you.
(gasps)
You're blind.
If anyone messes with this
kid. I will destroy them.
It's okay. No one's
messing with me.
You're not a freak.
and I won't let you
think that about yourself.
I don't think
I'm a freak.
So brave.
Hmm. Huh.
Um. this is the
last seat. so...
My side. your side.
Hi. Nikki.
I'm Bart.
This situation.
it's nuts. right?
Oh. look at you--
opening a book so you
won't have to talk to me.
Well. I'm just gonna be
tuning up the old armpit.
(blows tone)
(mimics sound
of passing gas)
Good news. children.
Everyone did well on this test.
except...
Lisa Simpson. F.
An F?
Okay. this is the time
when I always wake up.
Come on. alarm clock.
get me out of this.
(imitates blaring alarm)
Sorry. Lisa--
this F is all too real.
No it's not.
dream Hoover.
And as long as I'm asleep.
I'm gonna have some fun.
I can fly!
Wheeee!
(grunts. groans)
This isn't a dream.
I really did fail.
I take no joy in this.
(muttering):
Little Miss Perfect.
BART:
Whoa.
Damn. this
caterpillar can eat.
(gasps) Damn.
Damn!
Do you mind?
Oh. man. you girls ruin
everything-- even vampires.
Hey. vampires
are cool outsiders
who love girls
who hate cheerleaders.
No. they're all
about chomping neck.
And they don't put
product in their hair
like this loser.
They look like this.
NIKKI:
Awesome picture.
Can I draw a robot
barfing screws
on your arm with
my Sharpie?
I... I'd like that.
(laughing)
And... finished.
An F. An F!
I hope Harvard never finds out
about this.
(whirring)
Huh?
Can I teeter
while you totter?
Ever since you got
that bad grade.
you seem a lot cooler.
Lisa. you want
to come skip rope?
You can replace the tree.
Eat lunch with me.
Share my locker.
Come to my
birthday party.
Love me.
Wow. This is kind of great.
Lisa. can I speak
to you for a moment?
Uh-oh.
Looks like I'm in more trouble.
(chuckles)
Born to be bad.
(children laughing)
There was a mix-up
with your test.
(sighs)
You got an A-triple-plus.
Seems the F
belonged to Ralph.
I cheated wrong.
I copied the Lisa name
and used the Ralph answers.
CHILDREN:
Gifted! Gifted! Gifted!
I'm just advanced.
You can catch up.
CHILDREN:
Gifted!
Dad. I know we don't normally
talk about this stuff.
but there's this girl at school
I kind of like.
Anyway. I'm really
hoping you could...
Dad?
-Hey. boy.
-(screams)
(chuckles)
Your mother thinks
I'm working on the car.
Dad. that is genius.
but I need some advice.
Homer?
I thought you
were fixing my brakes.
(panicked screaming)
But I need to talk
about man stuff.
Talk to Grampa.
-He used to be a man.
-He did?
(grunting)
Give up the goods.
you yellow devil!
So. I kind of like this girl
at school.
but I'm not sure
if she likes me back.
There's one sure
way to find out
if a girl likes
you-- steal a kiss.
Really?
Did that ever work for you?
Sure did.
I remember it
like it was yesterday.
(static crackling)
Uh-oh.
Whoa.
She boards. too?
♪♪
So...
what should we do now?
Kiss her. ya idjit!
(sighs)
(shrieks)
Bart Simpson kissed me.
Oh. my God.
and that was my first kiss.
It will always be my first kiss.
Ew.
Say. "Haw-haw."
Haw-haw.
That was great!
Really great!
♪♪
Marge. Homer. this is Brody
and Madison McKenna.
Bart has been sharing a desk
with their daughter. Nikki.
Earlier today. your son
engaged in inappropriate
mouth-on-mouth contact
with our daughter.
You mean. he kissed her?
On the top
of the slide.
That's all
that happened?
And I got to miss work?
(chuckles):
Oh. I could kiss you.
Mr. Simpson.
I'm an attorney.
and my husband is
a federal prosecutor.
and neither of us is happy.
Well. maybe you guys
should look for easier jobs.
Unless you make this
an affection-free
environment.
we will sue this school
for its last dime.
All right. here it is.
And we will make you
regret the day
your son was born.
You're halfway home. lady.
It's not my fault.
Grampa told me to kiss her.
Why didn't you just tell
him to club her on the head
and drag her into a cave?
You mean second base?
Whoa. he's a little
young for that.
Well. if I talk to Nikki.
I'm sure I can...
No! If you go near her
one more time.
we'll be sued
into the poor house
and have to eat
garbage forever.
That's no problem.
Mom can make garbage
taste great.
Thank you.
Well. I mean it.
And it means
the world to me.
Well. don't worry. boy.
I know a wholesome way
to take your mind off girls.
(screaming)
This is awesome!
If only real life
was in 3-D.
(chuckles)
And the glasses smell
like the last guy who
wore them had pizza.
♪♪
(grunts)
(yelling)
(yell echoing)
♪♪
(squawking)
-(gunshots)
-Ha. ha!
-(both laughing)
-Look at that.
Oh. look at their guts.
He has blood
all over him.
(rapid typing on keyboard)
LISA:
"Dear fellow
organic gardening enthusiasts.
I'm afraid I am too sad
to post my list
of garden-friendly snails.
Yet again. I have seen
the bitter truth
of how difficult it is
to be smart and accepted.
With mulch love--
Lisa Simpson."
(laughs weakly)
Mulch love. That's cute.
(computer chimes)
Somebody posted a comment?
"Don't stop achieving
just yet. Lisa.
You are not alone. Flotus1."
Huh? Flotus1?
Who could that be?
SKINNER (over P.A.):
Attention. all students.
Please report
to an attorney-mandated
school assembly.
To make time for this.
the third grade's performance
of My Fair Lady is canceled.
(with British accent):
I say. that's rum news.
Very rum. indeed.
By now you've probably heard
that one of our fourth graders
did something
that a hundred years ago
would've been considered
innocent. but in today's
overly-litigious society
has been blown completely
out of proportion.
Now. what he said was...
I can hear.
The following skit. or sketch.
demonstrates the behavior
we wish you would save
for middle school.
And... action!
(light piano tune plays)
Oh. I'm just a wee little lass.
combin' me beautiful hair.
♪ Comb. comb. comb-ery doo... ♪
I'm Bart Simpson.
disruptive fourth-grader.
Oh! I finally caught one
of Bart's school plays.
That's not Bart.
It's Principal Skinner.
Bart's sitting
right next to you.
Yeah. now that I look closer.
that guy couldn't fool anybody.
Shut up. fatso.
-Why you little... (grunting)
-(choking)
-(snaps fingers)
-(Homer grunts)
(grunting and mumbling)
Now. players. recreate
the incident in question.
Ick. Ugh.
(kissing sounds)
Hey. Willie.
does he taste like failure?
(laughter)
Stop that laughter!
I can make these two kiss
all day. if I have to.
Hmm?
(grunts)
If you want them to keep
on kissing. just keep laughing.
(laughter continues)
(laughter fading)
(Bart sighs)
Maybe I did do something wrong.
(yells)
Oh. Bart. I hate
to see you like this.
(sighs)
Aw. look who's all confused.
Huh?
What the hell
are you doing?
I'm kissing you. stupid.
You're the biggest
psycho I ever met.
You wanna stop?
Absolutely not.
(sighs)
(Willie humming)
(groaning)
(gasps)
A VH-60N Whitehawk!
(thrilling music plays)
(children gasping)
First Lady
Michelle Obama?
(spits)
I flew in from Turkmenistan
because there's
a wonderful young person here
who's feeling
a little discouraged.
I sure am!
This young lady...
Oh.
...thinks just because
she's a high achiever.
no one will ever like her.
Huh?
Well. as I tell schoolchildren
all over the world.
I was a high achiever.
I got A's back
when A's were hard to get.
I was just like Lisa Simpson.
(gasps)
That's right. Lisa.
As an avid organic gardener.
I've read your blog.
Flotus1 is First Lady
of The United States one!
Yes. I wanted just "Flotus."
but someone had it.
That's me. 'cause I swim
with my flotuses on.
Everything I have
I got through academics.
I went to Chicago's
first magnet high school.
then Princeton.
then Harvard Law.
And now you're the most elegant
and popular woman in the world!
Well...
(laughing) I don't
know about that.
There's Carla Bruni.
Queen Noor of Jordan...
They're nothing compared to you.
It's not a contest.
But if it were. I think
we know how it would go.
But before I was who I am today.
I was a nerd.
So the lesson is. children...
I'll tell them
what the lesson is.
He's our Joe Biden.
Understood. So kids.
be nice to Lisa.
because the overachievers
will someday
be running the country.
and you don't want them
to be too screwed up.
Now. who else is
an overachiever?
Come on. now!
I am.
I am. too.
Fifth in my class
at Annapolis.
Scaled the summit
of the highest peaks
on six of seven continents.
Hey. that's great.
Don't forget to
bring the scooper
when you
walk the dog.
Ma'am. yes. ma'am!
Now. let's roll.
(grunting)
Sorry. ma'am.
We can't seem to reopen
the hatch to the copter.
You were saying?
Oh. well. I loosened it up.
That is the most
amazing thing
that's ever happened
to this school.
(laughs) Well. yeah. till
they find out about us.
What do you mean "us"?
Well. like. uh.
a-aren't you my girlfriend now?
Oh. you mean.
like you own me?
I'm sorry.
Ugh! You're always
apologizing.
Just tell me
what you want!
You should know
what I want!
I want you to act the same
way two days in a row! Ugh!
I'm not gonna let
you hurt me anymore.
(screams. thuds)
(crying):
He's dead!
I love him!
(breathing loudly)
Oh. he's breathing.
Loser.
He's stopped breathin'!
Who knows gob-to-gob?
You know. mutton hole
to mutton hole.
No one goes near that boy
till the ambulance comes.
Any physical contact violates
our school's no-touch policy.
Let's quickly prod him to the
curb with this pool skimmer.
Good thinking.
Move!
I know CPR!
Nikki. no!
I prefer a dead child
to a lawsuit from your parents.
♪♪
(exhaling)
(cheering)
Ugh! Ya call that a kiss?
-Come here.
-(whimpering)
(kisses)
(children chattering)
Nelson. now that
the ban's been lifted.
let me touch your face.
That way. I can see you
with my fingers.
Ew! I said your face.
not your butt!
Oh. you feel comfortable
enough to mock me.
-(grunts)
-(groans)
That's for mocking me.
Nelson. your punch
restored my vision!
I can see again!
Really? Kevin.
that's wonder...
Haw-haw!
The student has
become the master!
Nikki. thanks for
saving my life.
Look. can we just pretend
that never happened?
I don't want
everyone at school
to go around
thinking I like you.
I don't get you.
You're hot.
you're cold.
What is your deal?
Oh. Bart. you've got
a few things
to learn about women.
And I will never
tell you what they are.
I give up.
Smell ya later.
(sighs)
I love you!
♪♪
Shh!
Enhanced by Fotokem